# STEFAN MILENSKI

# **DETAILS**

#### **ADDRESS**

Bitola

North Macedonia

#### **PHONE**

+38971232205

#### **EMAIL**

stfnmilevski@gmail.com

#### **DRIVING LICENSE**

B category

## SKILLS

Adaptability

Communication Skills

Fast Learner

Computer Skills

Ability to Work in a Team

Ability to Work Under Pressure

Microsoft Office

### **PROFILE**

A self-starter and quick learner. Versatile skill set with experience in customer service, sales, and written and oral communication. Recognized skills in mentoring, mediating between employees, and in leading team projects. In my free time I like to skate with my rollerblades or take a hike in the mountains. My passion for music spontaneously evolved into a career as a DJ, playing music from local bars to international festivals. Along the way i had a privilege to meet beautiful people from all around the world and share unforgettable moments and life experiences.

# **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

Car Washer, Car Wash - Centar

Jun 2007 — Sep 2007

Waiter, Pizza Bure
Bitola

Feb 2009 — Oct 2009

Barman, Sun Love Happiness
Bitola

Jun 2010 — Sep 2010

Waiter, Trend Bistro Bar Skopje

Oct 2016 — Mar 2017

Hotel keeping, Hotel Zur Schonen Ausiht Gromitz - Germany

Jun 2017 — Sep 2017

Hotel keeping, Hotel Zur Schonen Ausiht Gromitz - Germany

Jun 2018 — Sep 2018

DJ BerryQyat, Local and international bars, clubs and festivals

Jan 2015 — Present

## **EDUCATION**

Economy, SOEU Jane Sandanski

Bitola

Bitola

Sep 2008 — Jun 2011

Economy and Management, University St. Kiril i Metodij

Oct 2011 — Present